What's up?
Jim.
How you guys doing?
Dude, I've been saying that all day.
Just going around saying Jim.
What's up people?
How you doing?
Narivan, Frank, Noni.
You make me think of the Starcraft pro called Noni.
Pastelero canino.
How you doing?
Yo, iLite33.
Thanks for subscribing.
Three months now.
And Frank, on six months.
It's your birthday!
No way!
Happy birthday, Frank.
Hope you're having a great day.
Hey,
can you tell us how many episodes of stania left?
Infinite.
It never ends.
When we reach the last episode, I start over.
And we just keep going.
We go round and round, round and round and round.
Exactly.
No, but I don't want to spoil anything in case you're...
Well, unless you really want to know, I can tell you.
Man, so it's so rainy in Denmark today.
And I had to go to the hospital earlier to get a CT scan.
My first ever, by the way, so I was really excited about it.
You know, going into that tube and everything's rotating and shit.
It's to do with the thing I talked about earlier.
It's nothing serious.
But on the way there, it started raining so much that I may as well have jumped into a pool when I arrived because my pants were completely soaked.
I was dripping water everywhere throughout the hospital.
And you know what's funny?
In the hospital in Denmark, I don't know if this is the same in the US or other places in the world, but they actually have adventure lines on the floor, leading you to different sections.
So I came into the reception.
I was like, I need to go to the scanning.
And they're like, follow the orange line.
So I was imagining the music playing, you know, it did not have the music.
Nope.
But I was imagining it.
It's to do with, I had some kidney stones earlier and they just want to check if everything's fine.
I'm doing fine.
I'm totally fine.
Well, hopefully, I haven't gotten the results yet, but I feel fine.
So should be good.
Good news is we've got a much better test for you.
Fighting an army of mantis men.
Pick up a rifle and follow the yellow line on the floor.
You'll know when the test starts.
Is that a reference to rig and Morty?
I'm not sure it sounds like something out of rig and Morty.
Drink plenty of water then?
Exactly Frank.
I've been doing that.
I've been chugging water and coke.
Well, not chugging coke, but mostly water.
Yeah.
Actually, technically sparkling water.
I love sparkling water.
They didn't scan my brain.
They scanned my uterus.
I'm sorry.
Okay, guys.
Nothing has been lost, luckily, in Neuter.
Hold on.
Everything seems to be functioning correctly.
There's nothing that went lost to the to the ether.
There we go.
Test, test.
Seems good.
Your scans.
No, so they had to scan my kidneys.
Just to check if there's any stones in there.
That's all.
It's nothing too serious.
Can you add a slight whistle sound effect whenever you do a transition?
I mean, it's a portal reference, guys.
I haven't played portal in, well, since they since it came out.
So very long time ago.
I have vague memories of that game, you know, the ending.
I have vague memories of the companion cube, stuff like that.
It's all very, very vague.
It's like a distant memory at this point.
So I don't get those references, unfortunately.
Can we get a video tutorial on the plopping sound?
So it's basically a whistle.
OK, like a short whistle that you do, like very shortly.
And then you modulate the whistle itself by doing a little kick with your finger on your cheek.
Man, I made it first time.
That's rare.
Let me try again.
Yeah, it's difficult.
I've actually gotten to the point where I can do it without the finger kick, but it doesn't sound as good.
Uncanny.
Oh, the uterus scan.
I couldn't remember the name of the male organ kidney.
So I just I was like that area of the body uterus, you know.
I just tried that.
You know, don't do it harshly.
Do it very gently.
You shouldn't hurt yourself.
Just a very slight tap.
OK.
Very slight tap.
Also, it helps to drink a little bit of water first.
Lubricate the mouth.
OK.
You're just pressing a button.
Don't lie.
I'm really not.
If I had a webcam, I would put it on.
And I'd show you.
It's true real.
It's true.
Damn it.
Oh, OK.
So I'm going to jump in.
OK, so here's the plan.
I'm not actually going to close you guys down for this one.
You're going to be on the side, but I'm most likely not going to read it very much because I get absorbed in the game.
But I mean, you know, we're going to try this.
I'm so deep in the game at this point, there's not really much to spoil, I think.
Wait, what's this?
A safe game with old version was detected.
Would you like to continue it?
Weird things may occur.
Oh, we highly recommend that you don't try to load pre 1.0 saves.
Everything will be broken and the gods will most definitely be angry.
What?
I didn't.
What is wrong with my save now?
It should be fine though, right?
Because this is not pre 1.0.
Let's see what happens.
Oh, what the?
No!
What the fuck?
I'm so confused.
Wait a minute.
Huh?
Guys.
What the fuck is this?
What is it?
Seed zero?
Hold on.
I think I made a backup of my world.
You guys told me that last time and that was such a good call.
Wait a minute.
Nala games.
I have it here somewhere.
Maybe I can revert the game to an earlier save.
I have it here, so.
The 17th of September.
That should be correct.
It says August now instead of April.
Okay, hold on.
I'm gonna quit real quick.
Is there a way to downgrade the game to an earlier version?
Make sure you back up the backup before unbacking up the backup.
Oh yeah, of course.
I would just copy it.
I wouldn't move it.
Yeah.
Let's see here.
Updates.
Background.
Wait, what?
I don't see a way to revert.
But I'm gonna try and copy over the folder.
Why is there always something wrong with the save?
Hold on, where was the save located?
It was like AppData something, right?
AppData.
Local low.
Nala.
There it is.
Found it.
Okay, and we put this here.
And then... Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Put it somewhere else.
Put it in the music folder.
Sure.
Just put it in there.
That's what she said.
Okay, Nala Games Neutec.
Copy it over.
Here we go.
It is being copied.
I'm excited.
I mean, it should be the same folder.
Unless some kind of cloud thing affected the save, you know?
Also, did I accidentally activate the cloud save thing again since last time it was bugging a little bit?
Privacy, betas, updates.
No, Steam Cloud is off.
Okay, it's copied over.
Let's try again.
It says build August 12th.
Ah!
No warning.
That looks better.
That looks... I mean, I don't quite remember exactly what it looked like.
But this is correct, no?
Hold on.
I'm actually quickly gonna check the VOD.
I just want to see the last frame of the VOD to see if that looked like this.
I have it here.
Let's just confirm 100% that everything... it looks fine.
But let's just see.
It was 35, wasn't it?
Where did I lock out?
Oh yeah, oh yeah, it looks exactly the same.
Perfect.
Very good.
All right, we're back.
That was weird.
So I think what must have happened is that the only thing I can imagine, something must have affected the folder with the save in it.
Somehow during the time between last time I played and now.
And I haven't launched the game at all.
So maybe there was some kind of update, like a small hotfix or something, that affected my save in an unpredictable manner.
And that's why it was all bugged.
But then I had a backup.
Man, guys, thank you so much for telling me to make a backup.
Otherwise this would be rip.
Amazing.
Okay, let's just remind ourselves what the hell is going on here.
So we have a pretty sick wand.
Look at that.
And I have black holes, infinite.
A very fast infinite black hole wand.
I have a healing wand, but it's a very special one.
And I jump into it and I heal like that.
I remember this now.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, baby.
Oh, and I'm also bleeding, I'm bleeding oil.
So we're being slippery here.
That was the issue with this one because I keep hitting myself and then I bleed oil.
Exactly.
Oh, okay, okay.
So the plan is... What was the plan?
Oh yeah, I wanted to do the music thing.
We wanted to do the music thing.
So in the frozen caverns... Oh my god, stop sliding.
In the frozen caverns, there's some sheet music there.
And I think I know exactly what it says in so A, B, C, D, E, F, G.
Those are the notes.
I don't even know if it's called notes, but it's like the musical thingies in the musical sheet thingy.
Okay, we got to get the musical wand and we got to play that sequence.
Something's got to happen.
I don't see any other way to perform music in this game.
And then obviously I want to go to east to get more perks.
I'm pretty sure I would.
It would be beneficial to find a better healing before we do that.
So this one is a temporary healing.
Optimally, I want to find the circle of healing so that I can keep black holding and healing at the same time, thereby saving a wand slot and use it for something else.
Now I have an empty wand here.
I'm not sure why I'd have that.
Probably just to be replaced by whatever I find in Wand Mart.
But I want to go find the musical wand now.
So let me actually keep this here.
Put this wand that I have currently equipped in my second over there.
So I don't actually need it right now.
And I have no idea where I am in the world.
Also, hold on a second.
Yeah, yeah, that seems good.
That seems good.
I'm so happy this save isn't fucked.
Such a good feeling.
Also need to remind myself what I have here.
I'm invisibility, melee immunity, exploding corpses, immune to electric damage, bleed flammable oil, and vampirism.
That's right, vampirism.
Not that we're gonna do much of that anymore.
I think we're past the point of sucking blood.
Right, we also gotta do this.
We gotta bring an egg here.
Egg, egg, egg.
You know what?
Let's see if we have an egg.
Is there an egg here?
There's so many spells.
There's gotta be... Ah!
Does that count?
Wait, summon rock spirit?
Could it be?
I could try it, I guess.
What else do I have?
Egg, egg, egg, egg.
Oh wait, I remember now.
I remember.
I left behind my teleport wand.
Didn't I?
I left behind my teleport wand because I needed a wand slot.
I think my original plan was to go to War and Mart now to find better healing, but I don't remember where I left my teleport wand.
Is that the one?
Hold on.
Those are rocks.
Man, I have really destroyed all of this, haven't I?
So I'm actually at the very bottom.
Oh no!
Oh shit.
I fucked up.
I forgot about that.
God damn it.
Well, wait, why am I taking damage?
What's happening?
Wait, what?
That was such a mistake.
I can't believe I've done this.
It's not the fastest way of healing, as you can see, but it works.
It definitely works.
And it's decently fast as well.
Let's just go up.
We have other places where we can change our wands, right?
Don't tell me that was the only place.
Oh no.
Because if that's the case, then we may have to go east.
Get out of here, you bastard.
I have to remember, I can just black hole everything.
Wait a minute.
So this is on three and four.
Gotcha.
Just keep going up.
In fact, just do that.
Also, the audio is bogging a little bit, I think.
There's no audio when I throw the black hole.
There is.
It's just very fast.
It's extremely fast.
Wait, did I see something?
I thought the screen just flashed and revealed something in here.
No, never mind.
Almost like a graphical glitch revealed something about the world there.
Oh, we're here now.
Right.
Is it just me or is there no sound on the floating that I'm doing?
Oh no.
Oh shit.
It is actually really annoying not having teleport, but it's the sacrifice we gotta make.
So where am I now?
Exactly.
Ah, we're here.
Okay.
Wait.
I gotta do a little bit of combat.
I gotta get back into it.
All right.
I'm back into it.
We keep moving.
Oh, that means a black hole.
You
just keep going up.
There's definitely no sound on the black hole anymore.
That sound is gone.
Oof.
The screen is shaking a lot.
Man, I'm so happy to be immune to electricity.
Did I just break something?
Hey, Hamis!
How are you doing?
We made it back to the hemisphere in record time, I would say.
That was so fast.
Now we gotta go up to the tree.
The tree.
And then I gotta look at my phone because I took a picture of of the melody we need to play.
Wait, what the fuck?
Wait a minute.
Are things blocked?
What the hell?
Why was there a chest there?
I don't remember that.
Also... Okay, so the seed no longer says zero.
I'm just curious.
That was so weird.
It said zero before.
I wonder if you actually manually start a game and seed zero if it will reproduce what we saw just before when it looked bugged.
I wonder if there are seeds that are just inherently bugged.
What's that?
Secretorum hermetis?
Wait, what?
Why is that?
Why was it invisible?
That's weird.
Okay.
So it should be right up here.
But they removed this part.
There it is.
Let's be careful not to destroy anything with the black hole.
Let's make one there.
Okay, so let me look at my phone.
Photos.
There it is.
Oh shit.
But I don't... Hold on.
Bring out the thing.
Also, one second.
Let's see here.
So the photo looks like this.
So I actually kind of forgot what I learned.
But I think I understand.
So hold on.
We have... Let me make it a bit thicker.
Like that.
Two, three, four, five, and then six, seven.
I don't know why those are shorter.
But basically, we have like a circle here.
A circle there.
One here.
One in between.
And one here.
So what this means... This is, I think, A.
B, C, D, E, F, G.
Unless it's the other way.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G.
Something like that.
Hold on.
Let me actually quickly Google Notes, Musical Notes.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G.
Oh, no.
Actually, it was weird.
It was like E, F, G, A, B, C, D, E, F, it seems.
Oh, that's such a weird... Okay, you can't see what I'm seeing, of course, but...
I think I'm doing it correct.
So this is A.
This is B.
This is...
Oh, I see.
Okay, so if it's inside a line, it's A.
If it's beneath, this one is B.
Oh, man.
This is gonna be terrible.
So hold on.
What would this be?
This would be...
A.
And the next one is here, which is... wait.
One, two, three... D?
D, I think?
D.
And then comes... No, we need this one first.
So wait.
Oh.
Emergency, go back.
This one is...
F.
Because it's the one on that line.
And then we have this one, which is... D.
Okay.
And then this one is in the middle of the line.
It's C.
No.
It's E.
And then comes the next one, which is on top of that one.
Hold on.
One, two, three, four...
It's on top of it.
It's A.
You know what?
I'm actually just gonna take all the notes with me.
Because... just because I don't want to come back here.
Okay.
So wait a minute.
We need... what was it?
A, F, D, E, A?
Oh, wait.
We don't have room for this.
Oh, fuck.
I didn't make room for it.
Uh, let's just throw away stuff I may not need.
Make a spell cast.
Immediately jump a long distance.
Maybe I'll get rid of this here.
I mean, these things I can always come back for, I guess.
Heavy sp... uh, petra... let's put that here.
Necromancy.
Let's put it down as well.
We don't need these.
At least not that many.
Tele... Oh, is that the one I used?
No, no, no.
I had a teleport wand.
Piercing shot.
Homing.
Maybe this is actually okay now.
Let's see here.
A... uh, what was it?
A, F, D, E, A?
Oh, wait.
There's no F.
Oh, no.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
A.
Oh, no.
We gotta go up.
Ah, I'm taking all of it.
Give me D, E we already had.
A, D, E, G.
Okay, that's everything, I think.
I don't need any of the... Oh, maybe I do need the shot.
Maybe I'm misunderstanding.
Shit.
Give me that one.
Also, I forgot to change it back.
There we go.
Okay, uh, let's try it.
Oh, but we have no place to put it.
There's no place to edit the wand.
Okay, so here's what we're gonna do immediately.
We're going east.
Right now.
We need to have a place to change wands.
And we should be able to make it if we go slow.
Well, I don't know.
I kind of forgot how much damage I took in the cursed rock or whatever.
Or was it toxic rock?
One of the two.
So now I kind of want to bring my teleport wand.
But I can't really make it, so I have to find the wand and I don't remember where I put it.
Hmm.
Just do that.
So here's my plan.
Since I have such a crazy black hole now and it's super fast, I'm gonna try and just delete the entire fucking mountain.
If there's no cursed rock at all within a mile, maybe I won't take damage.
I experimented a little bit with that last time, making it a little wide, but it wasn't that wide, you know?
Okay.
Oh man, I'm so slow without teleport.
So slow.
Wait, I have one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Oh wait, I have three more, of course.
Whoops.
Didn't mean to shoot that.
I also have faster levitation and I forget what the second one is, but I have the gamble.
Is it more gold or something?
Why can't I see that?
I can't mouse over it.
Wait, maybe if I...
Always cast, that's right.
I put an always cast on one of my wands using that, but it was random.
Whoop.
What's that say?
Oh yeah, right.
Mushroom below.
Here's everybody.
Wait, why is that blood so pink and not red?
Maybe it's just because of the desert.
Also, what's going on with this fucking skull?
Maybe nothing.
I should probably not have taken this wand with me just in case I find something else that I want to replace it with.
Maybe I'll just leave it on the pyramid or something.
God, am I slow without teleport.
I regret not taking it with me, but I don't know where it is.
Maybe I left it at the first mountain.
That would be a place to leave it.
It's either that or the last, but I already checked the last, so it's a little bit.
I don't know.
Also, I never went up here this run.
I don't think so at least.
May as well just do that now.
There's a boss here to be killed.
Oh yeah.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Gimme.
And I'm gonna go straight down.
Are you gonna wake up?
Wake up, sir.
Here he comes.
There he is.
Okay, he's gonna open his mouth and I shoot him.
Open your mouth.
Wide open.
Gimme a big smile.
There we go.
Oh shit, oh shit.
I think he closed his mouth again.
There you are.
Got him.
Not bad, huh?
That was pretty easy.
Too powerful for him right now.
What's this?
Decelerating shot.
Wait, what did I just pick up?
Oh, max health.
Nice.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Um, well.
Oh, I gotta translate this.
We gotta translate that one.
So wait.
Cookbook.
Uh, I want to go to here actually.
Zoom out a little bit.
Okay, so wait a minute.
I'm just gonna check if I already did it.
Question mark.
Teleport.
Wisdom through gain.
Friendship or Everest.
Wait, didn't I also have another one?
Teleport?
B.
B on the second.
Four and a B.
L.
I don't see... I don't think I've done this one.
Let me just see the first couple letters.
Maybe I'll remember if I did.
Question mark is Y.
Then we have that one, which is... What is that?
O.
Then we have the L and this thingy.
U.
Oh, your reward.
I've done this one.
It's gonna say your reward.
I've done it.
Never mind.
It's been a while.
Okay, keep going east.
We're on a mission here.
Ah, man.
Almost at a thousand HP.
Feels good.
So foggy.
I actually like it.
You know what I need?
I need a wand with a lot of recoil.
That's another way to get, uh, to travel fast when you don't have a teleport wand.
By the way, here's the plan.
If I can't make it through somehow, maybe if I, if my healing is too bad and I can't make it through the mountain, I'm gonna dig down instead and see what the hell is going on straight below.
Because I haven't tried that yet.
And now that I have infinite black holes, we're gonna do that.
I can't believe I actually destroyed the goddamn holy mountain.
That, that is, that is such a goddamn mistake.
It's unreal.
Let me through.
I'm actually afraid of hitting something I shouldn't with the black hole.
Like this, for example.
Not that it matters too much, I think.
Play some music for the local population.
Who I will soon decimate.
Yeah.
What is going on here?
See, these are the type of places where I want to try and just dig down.
It's bound to be something great, right?
Okay, here it is.
Let's see what's happening.
I need to see how much DPS I'm taking.
This is the easiest digging in the world.
Here we go.
Oh, wait, I bleed from that?
Oh, that's gonna make it terrible.
We got to clear a big area here.
Can I actually do this?
There's gonna be too much oil.
Oh my god.
Oh, dude.
Okay, we got to try and clear some more of this first.
That is insane.
Man, I think I could do it with my teleport wand.
Yeah, this healing is not fast enough.
If I need to heal mid, mid trip here.
No, it's not happening.
And the bleeding is making it worse.
All this oil.
This is the most scuffed thing ever.
Okay, let's go down.
Let's just go down and see what happens there.
Who knows?
What dangers lurk in the depths?
I don't want to go straight down.
That's a bit too scary for me.
All right, what do we got?
Look how fast I'm descending.
Whoop.
Wait, where am I?
Huh, no way.
Incredible.
Well, you know what?
I wanted to go here anyway to find wands.
That's perfect.
I got to find better healing.
That's the ticket out of here.
That's lovely.
All right, not what I need.
Not my tempo.
Anything special here?
Chaos magic.
Nah, sounds a bit too crazy for me.
Even for me.
Spitterbolts.
Whoa, how dare you, sir?
Last time I was here, I really got messed up by the Poland people.
Not to be confused with the Polish people.
Is that acid?
It is.
Let's not mess with that.
Uh-oh.
I messed with it.
No, I need water.
Or I just heal myself.
Wait, why is the acid?
No, wait, that's toxic sludge.
It's like, why is there acid everywhere?
Okay.
Do I even need gold?
The answer is yes.
There's very expensive things up in heaven.
And I intend to make a purchase.
Transactions will take place, okay?
Credit cards will get swiped.
Wait, I've been here already.
Have I?
It's explored, sort of.
That's concentrated mana, nothing to be afraid of.
HP, HP.
I really need horizontal acceleration here.
I am horizontally challenged.
And I am vertically amplified.
What's this?
Projectile energy shields.
By the way, another question.
So, the can't tell.
I wonder...
I probably don't need that to play the music.
I can just play the music with some other wants.
I don't need that specific want.
Another health.
Wow.
They're just giving it away at this point.
Damage plus!
Do I?
Nah, I'm doing fine, actually.
Heal me up.
What do we got here?
No healing.
I need the circle of variance.
Circle of resuscitation.
I need circles, that's what I'm saying.
Ah, not quite what I'm looking for.
Almost my tempo.
Further down.
Wait a minute.
Hey!
We're back!
Holy shit!
And hold on, it's a normal sized teleport.
You know what that means?
I'm gonna make a hole and just... through the hole.
We're gonna... through the hole.
But first, as I'm here, we're gonna try and find some healing.
Oh, wait a minute.
It spreads out, right?
Oh, that's funny.
So it's gonna go pop, pop, pop, depending on which one of those projectiles hit first.
Very interesting.
Sawblades.
What is this?
The White Palace?
I can make that reference now.
Just a year ago I couldn't, but now I can.
Circle of unstable metamorphosis.
That seems like a bad idea.
I
don't want to mess with that.
Reduce recharge.
That is intriguing.
But it's not like crazy intriguing.
It's just a little bit intriguing.
Oh!
Okay, here's the thing.
Acid is actually deadly to me.
Even though I have a thousand HP, acid is bad.
I've been here already.
That shit will kill you so fast.
You don't even know.
More health!
That's a thousand!
We did it!
1k HP, baby.
1011.
Beautiful stuff.
More wands?
I'll take it.
Ball lightning.
I've been here already.
Go further down.
Did I ever get high at all?
I don't think I did.
It's a little bit risky.
Hoodlums.
Ah, man.
The triple kit teleport is tickling me in the wrong place.
It doesn't feel good, you know?
It's like an uncomfortable tickle.
It's not quite the thing I enjoy.
What's that?
Polymorphine?
Get out of there.
How do I do this?
Probably just like that.
Oh, no.
It's not what I need.
I've been here already.
Further down.
Let's keep going down.
More health.
I will take it.
I mean, if I have enough health and I don't have teleport, I could just walk through the mountain.
If you have like a million health, I mean, that's a lot, you know?
But then you can just walk through.
It doesn't even matter.
Unless it's like percentage based damage that you take, similar to toxic sludge.
Then we have an issue.
Don't need that either.
Unstable teleportation?
I mean, I'll take the flask.
Thanks.
He says, even though it wasn't very intriguing.
Oh, once.
So many.
What's this?
Luminous drills.
Nah, not feeling it.
Okay, so now we're at the edge.
Let's go down from here.
Okay, so that's also the bottom.
Well, shit.
I feel so good not having to rely on blood right now.
Feels amazing.
What do we got here?
A chest.
Exciting.
Dynamite.
Oh, what's this?
Come on, please.
No.
Unfortunate.
That was very promising though.
Even more health.
Okay, I think it's time.
We just go.
I have teleport.
I have good feelings about it.
I think we can do it.
I'm going, man.
Let's go up.
If I destroy the entire mountain, it doesn't even matter if they're scattered on my teleport.
I will arrive somewhere.
Hopefully.
Oh, that's funny.
The actual pinpoint of light is slower than the teleport, so it arrives a little later.
That's a fun effect.
Which is interesting, because pinpoint of light sounds like it's photons, which should be the fastest thing.
But I guess not.
Wait, why am I not just doing this?
Ooh, okay, okay.
How am I going to do this properly?
Let me just make sure everything is cleared.
Do I just go for it?
Okay.
Worst case, we can go back.
Right?
I'm just going to turn around and hopefully we survive.
All right.
Wish me luck, guys.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm not ready.
No, no, no.
That was totally not my tempo.
We need to destroy... We need to do this in stages here.
Destroy this crap.
But what's happening?
Okay, okay, okay.
This is the most scuff thing I've ever seen.
The healing is cursed.
The rock is cursed.
My teleport is cursed.
It doesn't get worse than this.
Oh, all right.
I'm going to commit now.
We're committing.
Wish me luck.
Oh, oh, that wasn't too bad.
That wasn't too bad.
Oh, I thought it was way longer.
What the heck?
I have memories of that being 10,000 miles.
Guess not.
Cool.
We have arrived.
Am I going to arrive somewhere with that?
Wait, why?
Hold on.
Something's going on here.
Wait, are they hitting each other in the air?
What's going on?
Come on, give me teleport power.
That's not hitting anything.
What?
Well, I need to chill for a second.
Chill axe.
Okay.
We have arrived.
Oh, this is actually so exciting.
Remember, don't go through the portal.
For God's sake.
One job.
Don't go through the portal.
Just don't do it.
Like, why is this teleport bolts?
Not flying longer or farther.
Farther?
Further?
I think it's farther.
Guys, is it further or farther?
When I'm talking about distance.
It's father.
It's not mom.
Farther.
That's something else.
Okay.
Man, why is that so hard for me to say?
Farther.
Farther is physical distance.
Okay.
Thanks.
What's happening?
Get out of here.
I can't see shit.
Wait.
Where am I?
Just wait.
Wait it out.
Holy shit.
What the hell was that?
Okay.
I'm gonna splinter cell through this now.
I have invisibility.
Do not teleport.
What the hell?
Oh, wow.
He's just...
I'm neutralized.
Oh, fuck.
Uh, I hate it.
I hate it.
We're leaving.
I'm leaving.
Nope.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We are not doing that.
Wait a minute.
Burn him.
Ha!
Huh?
He's invisible.
What the fuck is going on?
I'm so confused.
It's fine though.
It's fine.
We're gonna, we're gonna go underground.
Calm down.
Look how big this wand is.
It's bigger than my body.
Doesn't this kind of look like that computer brand that everyone's making fun of because of the look?
I don't think I'm gonna... Should I tangle with you?
Nah, we're waiting.
No, no, no, no, no, don't be dumb.
Uh-oh.
Bro, they have some HP.
Can I please get through here?
East ancient laboratory.
Yeah, we're getting out of here.
What's that?
I'm scared guys.
I'm really scared.
Make a hole here.
Shit, it's the same place.
Oh no.
Make a hole there.
It's worms.
We can't die if we just make holes.
Undercover.
Nobody knows I'm here.
I'm scared of using teleport, actually.
I should play it safe.
Stay in... I'm stuck, I'm stuck.
Oh, there was a pixel on me.
Weird.
We're back.
Okay, so where do we emerge?
Ah.
Straight to here.
Wait, that actually confuses me.
Maybe I just don't remember the layout.
What?
Why are there chests?
Thanks.
There was also a chest in the central place.
My home.
Okay guys, we did it!
We have officially arrived.
Where did all this water come?
Oh, is it the same in east and center?
But there was also extra water there.
Ah, that's toxic sludge.
Let me actually just do it like this.
Wand.
Speed up!
Um, no.
I'm all right.
So, I didn't actually go get very far.
Last time I made it here.
Or did I?
I don't quite remember.
How did I die last time?
I think I died in the clouds in the last run where I made it to this place.
I got polymorphed.
And I died.
Don't take the portal!
Okay, calm down.
Come down.
Down from here.
Yes, yep.
Here we are.
Well, wait, we should be prepared to fight a boss now.
Where's the...
Huh.
See, here's... maybe to the right.
I mean, I'll find it.
Gotta keep... Oh, that's the east.
Okay.
Can't progress further there.
Although I kind of want to keep going right.
We got to try that at some point, too.
Just keep going.
Here we're going to go down and left.
Doink.
Oh, if you kick that, it explodes, I guess.
If you have an electricity thingy on you.
We made it.
Yeah, he's here.
Music.
He is here, but I'm not scared.
Am I?
Ooh, you angry now.
Oh, wait, you were already angry, so...
There you are.
Oh, shit.
Okay, he's nothing.
Easy peasy.
Here we go, we got perks!
Oh, that's so good.
Concentrated spells, faster projectiles.
I think I want to concentrate spells.
Lower spread and extra damage.
My one is lower now because of the reduced cast thingy.
Now we can edit.
All right, let me try the music.
We don't need all of these.
In fact, I would rather have my small teleport.
Anyway, so that's perfect.
So, let's see here.
What do we do?
AFDEA.
AFDE.
Oh, no, wait.
Did I fucking forget to take two of this?
Oh, wait, I didn't have an F.
Never mind, never mind.
Never mind.
All right, cool.
Put this there.
That's easy.
What do we have?
Hey, chainsaws.
I like chainsaws.
We take it.
In fact, just throw more on here, right?
Let's go absolutely bonkers.
Quadruple, so let's see here.
One, two, three, four.
Triple.
One, two, three.
Wait, one, two, three, four.
This one goes away.
It's still a little slow feeling.
Let's see.
Even worse.
That's interesting.
That's amazing, but we are running out of mana a little bit.
It recharges so fast.
I think it's actually fine.
I like it.
All right, cool.
What else do we have here?
Health and spell refresher.
We don't need any of that.
Oh, wait a minute.
982.
Guys, I have fucked my healing.
Never mind.
We do need the healing.
We do need these now.
Shit.
The concentrated spells.
Can I somehow...
If I get rid of that...
It's slower, but...
It will heal.
Okay, thank God.
Honestly, it's not that bad.
I need...
Dude, if I have a quick recharge...
Do I have something like that?
Oh, wait.
I have a heavy spread.
No, but that's gonna make it worse.
Also, let me take this.
I don't like the always cast on this one.
Although it does have a lot of mana charge speed, doesn't it?
That's kind of cool.
I mean, I don't...
I guess I'll keep it.
Grab this one.
Put it there for now.
Put it back.
And then put teleport on it.
Could even do that.
It looks a little funny, but...
It is what it is.
Projectile Thunderfield.
All right, man.
Let's just keep going down.
Let's find perks and let's find more wands.
This is gonna be a perk pinata.
And I'm excited.
Are you excited?
Let's keep playing.
Also, I suddenly have a shit ton of recoil.
Why is that?
What did I add?
Wait, why?
Huh?
That's weird.
I don't understand why I just gained a bunch of recoil.
Ah, we're just gonna go down.
No fear.
Actually, be a little afraid, because we could go down into unfavorable liquids.
So, let's be careful with that.
Oh, wow, we're right here.
The Instatide!
Gamble.
Should I do it?
Oh, I'm tempted, guys.
Ooh, I'm tempted.
It's a bit risky, isn't it?
I may just re-roll.
What's that?
Extra item.
Trick read.
I don't like any of these either.
Oh, I thought it was the other one.
Oh, hello, sir.
Get out of here.
I think I may...
God damn it.
I'll take it.
Stronger hearts.
Man, I kind of regret not doing the gamble.
Okay, nothing interesting in these wants.
We keep going down.
East snowy depths.
I have arrived, baby.
And the recoil is out of control right now.
But I guess it is a way to fly.
Don't take the portal.
Don't accidentally fall into a portal.
That would be terrible.
Whoa.
They're very angry with me.
That's fine.
Bring it on, dude.
Come here.
Oh, wait!
It's the big guy.
Oh, no.
Oh, don't tell me we lose here.
I got him.
God damn.
That's amazing.
Is that peace with gods?
Oh, wait, gas is near you.
Ignite automatically.
So here's the thing.
I am powerful and...
But the gods do scare me, guys, and I don't know if there's a third stage to this bullshit.
So I'm taking peace with gods.
I'm too afraid.
You just got to take it.
You got to take it.
What's this?
There's nothing there that I want.
Maybe the speed up.
Could be cool to have.
Get rid of...
chainsaw.
We have so many of them.
Yeah, that's fine.
Speed up.
We could put that on...
Wait a minute.
Maybe I like that more than light shot.
The hole is very fast, you know?
That's more manageable for me.
I don't like when it's too fast, okay?
Call me crazy, but...
I gotta go slow here.
Can I please get down?
Okay, let's not underestimate this place.
We have stroke a peace deal with the gods.
Wait, what?
My screen is full of bullshit.
Whoa!
What a shot!
I have way too much recoil!
What's happening?
Oh, wait a minute!
I...
I put light shot on it!
Wait, what?
How did that happen?
Oh...
That's too slow.
This... yeah.
Okay, wow.
I completely missed that.
You know what must have happened?
I had a chainsaw here and I wanted to put it back and I must have replaced it with a light shot.
Can I...
I get stuck here again, please.
I also need a better one for my black hole because it's... it's shooting too slow.
Oh, this is so much better.
No more...
Oh, that's... there we go.
There we go.
This is actually faster healing than before, somehow.
Like the net result of the healing is more, I think.
I shouldn't spend too much time here, actually.
I should just go through.
Do you want to play it safe, though?
There could be liquids here.
Unfavorable liquids and crusty jugglers.
I still have a bunch of recoil.
Still a shitty way of healing.
It's not great.
Why do I explore?
Just... just go down.
And we have made peace!
Nothing to be afraid of, ever again.
The gods look damn right, you do.
Oh!
Say it to Kivi.
Homunculus and boomerang spells.
What does that do again?
Hold on, let me stand here.
Your spells arc towards you, but gain extra speed and deal extra damage.
I mean, that could be nice with the healing, I guess, but...
Not so sure.
Matter!
Oh, finally, where have you been?
My beloved!
Oh, yeah, baby.
Possibilities have opened.
I'm thinking projectile thunderfield now.
Somehow.
Maybe not that one, but we can do some crazy shit.
I could put bloodlust on it.
Make it...
But that makes it scary to me.
Don't want to kill myself.
And extra damage, why not?
Just throw that in there.
Why the hell not?
We have the mana for it.
Heavy spread.
I don't want the rest of this, I don't think.
See what else we got.
All right.
All the fish died.
Is that a worm or what?
Am I gonna...
Should I take this or not?
I'm thinking.
12,800 to re-roll, I don't have that.
I don't like the homunculus.
I think I'll take the seta kiwi.
I wonder what happens if I use the seta kiwi here.
But if anything, I should use it at the very bottom.
Let's get rid of a flask.
Nice.
Put that there.
We have a seta kiwi.
Wait!
No, we're fine, we're fine.
I thought I left behind a wand.
I do wonder if there's another dragon boss here.
We should explore that.
Go all the way to the right.
Wait!
Teleport!
I forgot something.
I did forget something.
I forgot my teleport wand.
I was about to teleport and I was like, wait, why can't I teleport?
I just looked over at chat and everyone's just writing, ha ha.
Oh god.
This is what it's like, huh?
Wait, where did I put it?
There we go.
Did it.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This wand sucks right now.
This is bad.
We don't want chainsaws like that.
What if we just put them at the end?
Is that gonna make it...
It's gonna make it shit.
Okay, fuck.
Projectile area tell...
No, I don't want that.
Sigma copies every static projectile.
I feel like that's not that cool.
Maybe it is.
I don't know.
Heavy spread.
Let's get rid of that.
Now, you know what?
Just throw them away.
I'm fine with that.
I'm not mad.
This is totally okay.
Now we're talking.
Now, this wand...
You know what, actually?
Go back.
I'm changing this wand because it actually sucks for teleporting.
Put that there.
Let's find a one with a very low...
You know what I mean.
Shit.
There's no low of...
You know what I mean.
You know what I mean?
That one also sucks.
Wow!
Incredible.
I guess I'm forced to use this wand for now.
That's fine.
We're gonna get to another holy mountain in just a second here.
In fact, I may just go down.
I'm going straight down.
We want perks, baby.
Perks and wands.
That's what I...
Whoa!
Teleporting.
Oh, shit.
What the...
Where am I?
Circum?
I'll take that.
Let's drink some of that and go nuts here.
More black holes.
Cool.
That's something I require.
In fact, the Fungal Cavern is a great place to find some wands.
But I want to get perks first.
Kind of important.
Like, imagine I find Tinka with wands.
That's the dream right now.
Oh, hold on.
Let's not accidentally collapse.
Look the other way, bitch.
Protectile repulsion field and greed.
I feel like greed could be huge.
We do need lots of gold.
You can double...
Like, double the gold is very nuts.
I think that's very much needed.
Hello.
What the hell's that?
Invisible spell?
What?
Is this?
Turns to projectile invisible.
Huh.
And reduces castor lay.
That's...
Okay.
Purchase weakening curse melee.
Couldn't that be kind of sick with the chainsaws?
Costs 50 mana drain, though, and this adds 30.
This is gonna make us oom before you know it.
Uh, but we can try.
Let's put it...
Actually, I could get rid of the large spear bolt.
That is 25 mana.
And then put another chainsaw in there.
Put this over there.
Let's see here.
We have one, two, three...
Wait.
One.
Two, three, four.
One, two, three, we can add another one.
But then it's slow.
What's...
See, I'm sorry.
I don't even want to know why it's slow.
I honestly...
Oh, you know what?
Maybe it's better to put the weakening curse on the spark bolt itself.
That makes more sense to me.
That way the spark bolt hits them with the weakening curse.
And then the chainsaws go in and they go...
You know?
That's how that works.
What's this?
Explosive detonator.
All nearby explosive spells cast by you instantly detonate.
What?
I'm keeping it.
And that is knockback.
Reduce spread.
Formation trifurcated.
Pre-charge.
Um...
Vacuum field.
I think I'm good here.
Let's just move on.
Uh, go down.
Blop.
We have arrived in the eastern vault.
A scary place to be sure.
Whoa.
Why do I have so much recoil again now?
Is that the weakening curse doing that?
Maybe it was always this bad.
I don't know.
Wow, he just died.
Kill them all.
You know, if I find a reduced recoil, I will use it.
That's something I really want.
What's that?
Nothing that I want.
Oh, the meat.
There's a chest inside.
Wow, so much lightning.
Okay, we made it.
Sort of.
Fuck yeah.
What do we got here?
Ooh, a reduced recharge.
That is very intriguing.
I may purchase that.
No!
I thought it was...
Well, unlimited spells.
Is that even needed?
I'm thinking.
I'm thinking...
Protectile repulsion sector.
I don't think I want unlimited spells.
I'm gonna be honest here, this...
I can already make unlimited spells.
With my spells that I found at Yalchimisti.
I'm taking that.
Heck yeah.
That's also gonna protect me against polymorph.
If they shoot those projectiles at me, if I can blow them back.
That's more valuable than anything.
That's what I'll say about that.
So why did I need this again?
Reduce recharge because I needed to put it here.
That's right.
Another one.
Wait.
Recharge time.
It is better, I think.
Oh yeah.
Way more flying at the same time.
But we are limited by recharge though.
0.33, 0.33.
What is that sound?
Oh, the fish are burning.
This one adds reduces cast.
Why is this not completely instant?
This should definitely be zero in both castalay and recharge.
Ah wait, this adds 0.25 in castalay.
That's what's happening.
That is what's happening.
So if we add...
No, no, not that one.
Where's this one?
Oh, but then it's gonna be randomized.
Yeah, that's no good.
Fuck.
But I mean, it's better.
Look at this.
This is way more efficient.
The healing is definitely happening.
Now there's an egg I could take, but I'm not gonna.
Actually, I am gonna.
No, it's 5,900.
I can't.
It's too expensive.
Good thing we picked up the greed.
Whoa.
Wait, what's happening?
Wait a minute.
Oh, I forgot to put that back.
So that's that's weird.
Way that works.
That's kind of funny.
I do actually want to check the ones here.
Oh, electric charge.
Could be pretty big.
I'm taking it.
Hold up.
I'm putting electric charge on my damage wand.
I'm completely immune to that shit.
So I don't care.
Put it here.
Oh, that's awesome.
Look how cool that looks.
In fact, put it here.
Does it even matter?
Maybe not.
That's amazing.
Then I'm going to change this one back with whatever I had before.
Actually, I just realized this one does reduce recharge or cast delay.
If I put that here.
No, wait, we are limited by recharge.
It's not cast delay.
I guess I just don't understand what's happening.
The interaction that's going on here in this one is messing with me.
Cast a copy of the last spell in your wand.
Which is that one.
And that one is being...
Or maybe if it's a copy, it's not being affected by...
So if I remove these...
No, it's definitely affecting it.
Why is it not faster?
That's what I don't understand.
That's okay.
All right, let's go.
Get electrified.
That's going to stun enemies.
That's actually so big.
I feel like I'm making smart choices here with my wands this time around.
And the spells I put in them.
Like, think about it this way.
If there's an enemy that is really scary, he shoots polymorph shit.
I stun him with the first shot.
It's going to be so valuable.
Like, it's not the damage that I want right now.
It's the survival.
Can you guys please go away?
I should be picking up gold, by the way.
Whoa, be careful, be careful, be careful.
That guy will mess you up.
Oh God, that was a teleporter.
Yes, my healing wand sucks.
If anyone's wondering.
But it's my healing wand.
Uh-oh.
Bye-bye.
Wait, he didn't even die.
Now he died.
I'm doing so much damage.
Imagine I get...
I don't even know.
Two more Admanas.
Then I can start to go really crazy.
All right, let's just go down.
Don't be afraid.
I am afraid of that, though.
Oh, blow it away.
Did you see what...
That's a thingy.
That's a polymorph.
Repulsion field, dude.
Man, this wand feels good.
Except the recoil.
Everything but the recoil, actually.
Like, I need the money.
If I don't get the money, I can't even afford anything at the next holy mountain.
Holy healed.
Wait, those are wands!
Oh, only one.
Holy fuck.
Another reduced recharge?
It's tempting.
But I'm not taking it.
I'm gonna go down.
Down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
Wait.
Oh, wait a minute.
Was there no final one down here in the east?
I have memories of walking aimlessly in here last time, not finding shit.
Goddamn.
I think that's the case.
Yep.
So, what I'm gonna do...
I'm gonna go up again and I'm gonna find the...
Wait.
I hear teleport?
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, right.
Wait.
Don't take the portal.
I'm gonna find wands here.
Damn!
Even more damage.
But I think I have enough?
For now?
Like, I'm okay.
Maybe a freeze charge could be fun, but that's...
That is gonna freeze things, which is kind of annoying sometimes.
For me, that is.
Why a bolt with trigger?
Actually, hold on.
I may have...
I may regret not taking the unlimited spells.
You could put, like, really insane spells on your wand and you don't...
In that case, you don't need to have...
those Yalke Misty spells.
Just blow shit up.
I love the way the little electrical sparks work on these guys.
What are they called again?
The bubble sparks.
Such a cool effect.
Makes them look way cooler.
That's all that matters.
If you look cool, then you're winning.
So I'm gonna explore...
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
None of that, sir.
I'm gonna find some more wands here.
Just give it a quick look.
Yo, wait a minute!
Do we have a...
One more 2.0?
I... I'm gonna check it out.
We're gonna check it out.
Walmart.
I pretty much exhausted that place in the central location.
My main hub.
Assuming the layout is the same...
Let me see here.
We are currently here.
Uh, so if I go...
Oh, wait, if I go right, I go into a scary place.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I think you know what I'm gonna do.
Wait, what happened?
Wait, did I...
I forgot how this works.
Wait a minute.
Don't go that way.
Oh, wait, I still have the map on.
Whoops, sorry.
Here we go!
Hahaha, there it is!
Let's run it up the flagpole and see who salutes.
What I'm trying to say is, let's see what comes down.
All right, let's go.
Straight up again.
Actually, I regret my actions.
I'm an idiot.
No, no, I don't.
I don't regret it, actually.
I'm fully...
No, I'm totally accepting of this outcome.
Yes, I'm happy.
I'm very happy.
Uh-oh.
Things are falling.
Okay, this is getting a little sketchy.
I don't know about this.
I don't know what the fuck that was just now, but it hit me straight in the face.
Things are falling down.
Scary stuff.
You die, you die, everyone dies.
Whoa!
Oh, Christ.
This is kind of funny, actually.
I like it.
Reminds me of that one scene with Thor.
I forget which movie it is, where he goes.
I like it more!
And he just slams the cup on the ground.
What have we got up here?
Water.
And some detritus.
So, hold on.
I need to go precisely...
I guess snowy depths will do.
Or even at the very top could do up here.
That's not a bad idea either.
Although, if I go from...
Oh, wait.
We can try the Dragon Cave now.
And apparently...
So, platform room.
That was so mysterious.
Let's try and see if that one is located here, too.
We're gonna go this way.
Straight east from the Dragon Cave.
Let's see if we can find a Dragon Cave here, even.
Maybe it's not even here.
Who knows?
Gotta figure it out.
Uh, okay.
All the way to the east.
Whoa, that's a big open area.
Okay.
You know, having the pinpoint of light on the teleport is kind of sketchy.
Because, let's say, I teleport into a flask of polymorph.
And I break it.
I'm instantly polymorphed.
So, we need to find...
We need to fix that.
Pretty soon.
This is way too much of a risk.
Wand?
Hell yeah.
1800 mana max.
Damn.
What's that?
It's a spider!
I'm not even that afraid of them anymore.
Another nullshot.
Critical on burning.
Reduce recharge time.
Ah, man, I wish I had Tinko with wands everywhere.
All right, we're here.
East Dragon Cave!
It's real.
Wake up.
Wait, wake up, wake up.
Wait, what is the trigger point here?
There we go.
Wow, he died fast!
Holy shit!
No problem!
Damn!
All right.
Knockback.
Another electric chart.
Nah, I'm not feeling it.
I'm not feeling it.
Okay, go straight east.
Let's see if we can find the platform area.
Is this...
Black Hole always shooting a little too high.
I think it's because of this field.
Messing with the...
What am I calling it?
The projector.
Oh, here we are.
The path.
What is this place?
That is so mysterious.
There's nothing here.
What else do I go from here?
I think I go...
Have I ever tried just going straight east from here?
Let's try that.
Straight east.
And the good news is, if I end up encountering a...
Cursed Rock, I know I'm somewhere here, right?
Assuming that this is, of course, the same as the main world.
That means if I end up there, I know approximately where I am.
I can go a little to the left and then up to arrive in Want Mart 2.0.
I think that makes sense.
Let's go, boy!
Also, I should probably heal a little bit since I can.
No reason not to be full HP.
I'm actually disgusted, guys.
I'm disgusted with this perk.
Where is it?
That one.
No, this one.
I love one part of it.
I absolutely despise the other part.
It is just so bad.
But the positive that it gives is definitely worth it.
East desert.
Uh-oh.
Okay, keep going east.
Keep going east.
What the hell is that?
Huh?
I have never seen that!
Oh, shit!
Meat realm!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Nope.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
We're not doing that.
That place is fucking crazy.
And you know what the funny thing is?
Last time I was here, I had vampirism, right?
And I was on the brink of death, I think.
And I was like, salvation!
There's blood everywhere!
This is my kind of place.
Turns out, you can't drink it.
Wait, I'm filled with some kind of bullshit.
Kill me.
Go like this now.
So if the meat realm is here, it stands to reason that...
The overgrown cavern should also be there.
So echo a little higher up to get out of it and then right.
That's what I'm gonna do.
So happy to be immune to electricity.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Okay, okay.
So now I go up.
I know exactly where I am.
And I'm gonna go up here.
Hold on, one sec.
I'm gonna be there.
No?
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Oh, wait, there's no way I'm there already.
I thought I was here.
There's no way I'm there.
I must have been...
Somewhere here.
We're not...
We're not there yet.
Nevermind.
So this is just like some other place.
Kind of want to see what's going on.
Here we go.
We have to keep going east.
Okay, it's time to do the maneuver again.
Wait, I need to make a little bit of an area here.
Ah, so difficult to catch.
What?
There we go.
Okay.
Wait, why am I doing this?
Just go around it.
If I can.
Wait, I don't remember this even being here.
Cursed rock?
Wait, it's also up here.
Wait, it's not hurting me.
Okay, it is hurting me.
I got it.
Oh my God.
No, it's still there.
What the fuck?
Oh, wait a minute.
Is it actually hurting me if I make a path here?
I say I do that.
Yeah, it is.
Okay, up.
We've got to go around this crap.
This should be more than enough.
Hey, okay.
So there is a small region with the cursed rock for some reason.
So I am curious what's in there.
There's got to be something inside of that region.
So where exactly is that?
That would be...
Hold on, I went up from meat realm.
That was...
I'm in sand cave and it's got to be here.
I think there's something here.
Let me make a proper rectangle there.
Okay.
For the future.
Oh, I know where I am.
I'm here.
So wait, if I'm there now and I went up...
Right.
Yeah, this should be approx...
I mean, this is very approximate, of course, what I have there.
But this is fine.
East orb room.
Look at that!
Orb of corrupted knowledge.
Oh, heal it up.
Keep healing.
Dude, I found the perfect way of healing.
Watch this.
If I go up and to the right and I just keep walking, I can keep healing.
That is so fast!
That is incredible.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Who's shooting?
It's you, huh?
You little bastard.
Dude, my wand is nuts!
Love the electricity!
So good!
I hate this poison, though.
It's a real bomber.
Damn, I'm just rolling these people.
Nice.
You know what's funny?
If I do this and I hit myself with it, I always put oil in myself, which is a way to clear poison, I guess, or any other status effects.
So it serves as a double... well, the bad thing about taking the damage is kind of a good thing also, in a way.
Here we are!
East Overgrown Cavern!
We have arrived, baby!
The dream is real!
That's amazing!
Slime potion, no thanks!
Immediately find some healing, not the one we need though.
Or want.
I was trying to be systematic this time.
I know that's a joke whenever I say it, because I never do it, but I'm gonna go right now, then down, then left.
Oh my god.
And hearts give more health!
Wait a minute!
Does Berserkium increase the healing done as well?
Or is it only the damage?
Hmm.
Interesting.
I felt like I healed very fast there.
Okay.
Already I am deviating off of my systematic approach to all this.
That's fine though.
Like I said, I was just kidding.
Oh no!
Stay focused, focused.
Okay, okay.
Everything's good.
Invisible.
Two wands here?
Wow.
Hall!
Damn.
Wait, did I just pick something?
Oh, I picked something up.
I didn't mean to.
Whoop!
Throw it away.
So here I've already been, I think.
Yes.
Now we go down a bit.
Then we go right again.
Fire bombs.
Not really what a man needs.
I feel like there's a lack of wands here compared to the main hub.
This is Costco at best.
Actually, I don't even know if Costco is smaller or not, but it sounded funny.
Yeah.
Like what's a small chain in the U.S.?
Like Whole Foods or something, right?
Money.
Nope.
Come on, game.
Give me what I need.
Ooh.
Critical on wet water.
In parentheses, enemies.
And a plasma cuter.
No.
Now, if you find one that gives critical on oiled enemies, now then we're talking.
I would love that.
Whoa.
I think I'm playing a little too fast here.
I gotta slow down.
Things are getting a little too crazy.
What's this?
Intense?
No.
Ah, no.
No, no.
Reduce lifetime.
Nah, I'm okay.
I'm okay, bro.
1400 health, man.
We are accelerating in making our health a little bigger here.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I thought that was polymorphism for a second there.
I got so scared.
Every time I see pink, I'm scared.
Any type of pink.
Scared out of my mind.
Plasma beams.
You know, those could be fun to try and play with.
Like imagine putting homing on those.
Just fucking put a homing on a plasma beam trigger or something.
No, come here.
Come on.
Give me the one thing I need.
The one thing I want.
Nothing.
What's that?
Anti homing?
No.
Wait, there's another one.
At mana.
See, now I'm intrigued, but I can't take it home.
I may also have to let go of the...
I didn't think about this, but I obviously need to get let go of my teleport.
If I find the thing I need.
But I do have extra teleport, so it's okay.
And I can always come back here, I guess.
And an easy way back, actually, is to just take a portal.
Oh, but wait a minute.
Didn't I leave this in the holy mountain in this place?
In the east?
I think I may have done that.
Maybe it is better to just go back there.
And so that's the only place we can change our wand.
Haha, the electricity is so nice.
Speed up.
I just jumped in the water and everyone who was bathing with me just died.
Like this screen has so much going on right now.
Neuter is crazy.
Like, just look at this.
So many effects happening at any given time.
Wait, what's happening here?
I'm being confused.
Who is it?
Who's doing it?
Nothing there.
Man, the pollen is still dangerous.
Thunder.
See, that's the sort of thing that I want to put on my wand and just spam it.
If I have enough mana, of course.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, acid is scary.
There's too much of that acid there.
Good thing the black hole doesn't destroy wands, huh?
Healing, but not the one I need.
Whoops,
light shot.
No.
Oh, we got stuff down here.
Increase lifetime.
Critical plus.
I would like to take that if it wasn't for the fact that I didn't have Tinker with Wands.
I found so many damage plus in this run.
It's wild.
I found like 10.
And sometimes you never see them.
Oh my god.
Plasma beams.
Oh, look at all that gold.
Oh my god, I gotta take it.
That is too juicy.
18k gold.
It's not even that much.
Sawblades.
I mean, I'm immune to melee.
Maybe not the worst idea at some point.
Homing sawblades.
No, it doesn't work like that.
Those would be the Giga Disc projectiles.
This is a modifier.
Whoa.
Stop shooting that at me.
Oh, come on.
Give me what I need.
Dude, the ultimate wand is a wand where you have healing on both your attack wand, whenever you shoot and teleport and black hole.
Just whatever you do, you're always healed.
Disc projectiles.
Show me something good.
A holy bomb.
It's not something I want.
Did you notice how enemies get stunned immediately when I hit them?
That is so big.
More teleporting.
Ah, vacuum field.
Have I been here already?
I have.
Well, I'm getting lots of wands exhausted here.
Really combing the area.
Combing for goodies.
Been here too.
How about we go up from here?
Hey, sweet.
Sweet.
I keep thinking the death crosses are healing.
Like Giga healing.
I don't need that.
I don't need that either.
Oh, look at all.
Wow, there's so many hearts.
What the fuck is going on?
I've never seen this many so densely packed.
Kind of amazing.
Holy shit, that's a lot of black holes.
Black hole with death trigger.
Always cast it.
That's wild.
That's always black hole one.
Just like that.
I'm tempted to take it.
Hold on.
Yeah, I'm tempted to take it.
Because if I do that, I can save the towel for something else.
You know?
Yeah.
But I would have to come back, I guess.
Okay, we're at the edge here.
How was that?
Okay, I'm getting to the point where I would love to go through a portal and go back.
No, no, no, we're gonna go right.
That was the plan.
I want to see if we can go even more right.
Let's do it.
I got a heal first.
Look at that.
1780s.
Is that the most HP I've ever had?
It may be actually.
Oh yeah, okay.
I think I just go for it.
All right.
Wish me luck.
Oh wait, that wasn't too bad.
Oh, it got a little bit scary.
It got a little bit scary there.
I'm not gonna lie.
Half HP.
Look at all the oil.
I want to be full HP before I do anything else.
Absolutely playing it safe.
Okay, let's go.
I have no idea what's gonna be over here.
Oh, wait.
Shit, shit, shit, get it, get it, get it.
Is it actually just repeating?
There's... wait.
Infinite?
Infinite perks?
No way.
I forget I can just do this.
Also, someone's behind me.
Scares me a little bit.
Oh my god.
What's happening?
We got another angry guy?
The fuck?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck that, fuck that, fuck that, fuck that.
Fuck that, fuck that.
Nope.
There's no way we get infinite perks.
That's just, there's no way.
Uh-oh.
What the fuck happened there?
Okay, calm down.
In fact, I'm gonna stay below here.
I'm too scared.
We are worbing around.
Underground tactics.
God, this teleport one sucks.
We really gotta fix that one.
Oh, shit.
Making progress.
I wonder what this is gonna say.
Is it gonna say east, east?
Shit!
Run!
Dude, this place is dangerous as hell.
There's bosses everywhere.
God damn.
Huh.
Another chest.
It's actually just repeating.
What's it gonna say?
It doesn't say anything.
What?
All the pooping feeling is here, guys.
And it's bigger than ever.
I am not supposed to be here.
This is not good.
I feel like the game is breaking.
It's like, it's not so, I'm not supposed to do any of this.
Wait, why is everything... Wait a minute.
Why do I have vision of everything?
What the fuck?
Please, please, man.
Please, man.
Please, please.
Ah, fuck.
Wrong side.
You see that?
I pushed the dynamite back to him.
I did it intentionally.
I did it to hurt him.
Oh my god.
This is crazy.
No way.
What the heck?
The end is never the end.
Jesus.
Your projectile spells have a chance to duplicate, but you're more vulnerable.
Every time an enemy near you dies, you release mana recharging liquid.
The projectile is near, you slow down.
Hmm.
We roll.
How about it?
How about we try enemy radar?
Yeah.
Let's try that.
You can sense nearby enemies.
Oh, that's funny.
Look at that.
Yo.
That means you can shoot them off screen.
Yo, that's awesome.
Oh, why is everything revealed here?
Have you noticed?
Look, there's no fog of war.
This is so mysterious.
The weird thing is these enemies are not more difficult than usual.
They're just enemies.
Oh my god.
I just keep...
Goldenog is gravitate towards you.
You know what?
Why not?
Hell, what's happening?
Why?
Are the gods angry?
What's happening?
They look the other way, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is nuts, guys.
This is the craziest run I've ever had.
Okay, let me check if there's any better ones here for my actual teleport.
Because the one I have right now is Atrosia.
See, this one is actually better.
I'm buying it.
Put this here.
There we go.
Oh my god.
Oh, so much better.
That feels incredible.
Infinite perks.
I haven't even realized the potential here.
This is huge.
It is massive.
Oh, look how much they look the other way.
Extra life one off.
Dude.
Yes.
Planet ultra safe.
Ultra safe, man.
Oh, you know what, actually?
I'll be taking a freeze charge.
Yeah.
I'm gonna put that on here.
Just make it even more insane.
Just add all kinds of bull crap to it.
This is the ultimate omnidirectional damaging wand.
I don't know how else to say it.
It can do a little bit of everything.
It's the jack of all trades.
It's great.
I can see all the enemies.
So I'm guessing... so there's also a wand radar or something.
I'm guessing that's gonna do the same thing like this.
Just show me where the wands are.
Which doesn't sound too bad, actually.
That sounds really useful.
I have actually become a god.
I'm a god.
I can't die.
I am... invincible.
Completely invincible.
This way.
Extra health.
50% more maximum health.
Oh, but wait.
Call me crazy, but I want this.
I have vertical.
I can go vertical, but I can't go horizontal.
I'm taking it.
Call me crazy.
But that's gonna be so much more comfortable.
So much more comfortable.
I actually want this.
Man, this wand is looking nuts right now.
Damn.
My damage wand is insane.
Accelerating shot, no thanks.
I don't even care about enemies.
I'm going straight for perks.
Wait.
Extra wand capacity.
The wand you're currently carrying gain one to three additional spell slots.
Yo, that couldn't be too bad.
I mean, it's a crazy good wand.
Wand of swiftness wouldn't be too terrible to have more slots.
One.
Yeah, cool.
Why not?
I have infinite perks.
Why do I care?
I don't care.
I love it.
Oh my God.
This is amazing.
I've never felt like this.
I feel good.
I feel strong.
I'm actually getting kind of low on health here.
Wait, am I freezing myself here?
So I should probably improve my healing wand here, huh?
It's getting a little scuffed.
We can definitely make that one better.
What's this?
What is that?
Circle of displacement.
Oh.
Feared by worms.
Worms run away from you and worm and looky enemies no longer destroy terrain while burrowing.
Huh, I've never seen this one.
Mournful spirit.
Dying creatures leave behind a spirit that deals damage.
More love?
Why not?
I think I like more love.
Make creatures be more friendly.
Down we go.
Just straight down.
What's that?
That's the gig of death.
The gig of death.
Kind of nice with the gold gravitating towards me.
Oh wait, did we reach the end?
Oh shit.
You know what that means?
You know what that means.
Because I know what that means.
We're not done.
I'm not fucking leaving.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
That is a little bit scary.
What is over here?
Uh, what?
Oh.
Scary.
Dude, being able to see everything is kind of weird.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
Don't care.
Okay, that actually dealt a lot of damage to me.
I should heal a little bit.
I need a machine gun black hole wand.
Okay, off we go.
Man, it even reveals invisible enemies.
That's lovely.
I keep going right.
Wait, there was also a boss here somewhere.
Remember?
Wait, that's how I died last time.
At least the last time I had a good run.
Meteor.
Come on, gold.
Oh, I thought they would follow me forever.
Okay.
No, man, I'm not gonna fight any bosses here, man.
I'm gonna... I'm perk hungry.
I'm going straight for the perks.
Oh, you know it.
Heavy, heavy shot.
Plus 44 damage.
Damn.
Too bad I can't tinker.
Don't you dare shoot shit at me.
That was a bit scary.
Wait, am I back in Walmart?
What the fuck am I?
I'm really deep.
So where the hell am I?
Oh, no.
Nope.
Or maybe.
No, no, no.
What the... Oh, that's right.
There's also this place.
I was here once.
Completely forgot about this.
Oh, man, they have HP.
Yeah, I remember that.
They're very hard to kill.
Fuck that noise.
I'm just gonna take a quick trip through this place, if you don't mind.
See ya.
See, that's an efficient healing there.
Holy... so many spells on that one.
I'm actually poisoned.
Or toxic wasted.
Wait, why do I have a thing on me?
Someone is shooting me.
Oh fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
What the fuck is going on?
It's getting a little scary.
I'm not gonna lie.
This, this, this.
No good.
I'm just gonna leave.
Getting the hell out of here.
Get in here, get in here, get in here, un-chill for a moment.
Chill out.
Chill the fuck out.
God, I hate this healing.
It's so annoying.
Whoa!
He followed me all the way here.
All right, this works.
I mean, it's very annoying to do.
But you know, it is what it is.
I honestly have no idea where I'm going.
That's kind of cool.
Ooh, is this the spot?
Go.
Go, go, go, go.
We're getting good at this.
We're getting good.
Where will we emerge?
Aha!
We actually made it.
It actually just keeps going.
Oh, my goodness.
Why, though?
Like, why is this even a thing?
So mysterious.
That was sick.
Oh, this is hella effective.
Oh, oh.
Am I scared?
Should I be going on the ground?
I think I should.
Look how fast I'm traversing the goddamn world.
I'm breaking new ground here.
You wouldn't think this was Noisa.
When you look at this, this just looks absurd.
There's always a chest there.
I'll take it, sure.
Wait, what?
Why am I shooting so fast?
I'm so confused.
Oh,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute.
Oh, my God, it's still here.
Oh, man.
This is fun.
I love it.
What is that noise?
Every time I pick it up, rumble and someone is getting mad, it seems.
Did it stop?
It stopped.
Why am I checking these ones?
Slow
down there, cowboy.
Slow down.
Oh, my God.
There's just infinite perks.
Wait, always cast?
A random always cast spell is added?
That could be fun to try.
It could ruin the wand though.
Wait, hold on.
Get out of here, dumbass.
What is this one?
Liquids freeze in your presence.
I don't like that.
But then again, close call.
You gain additional chance to deal critical hits as long as there are enemies near you.
I am tempted to try this.
Do it.
What did I get?
Oh, no.
What are the chances?
God damn it, man.
Tell me.
You know what?
Let's try this one.
Let's see if this one works.
Let's just quickly... Ah, fuck.
It's not gonna work.
210 mana max, 86.
Actually, it has a higher mana charge.
I have a feeling this will work just fine.
Let's see here.
It's not gonna be as good though.
That's the thing.
It's kind of a bummer.
Wait,
wait, yeah.
Maybe I dropped the freezing.
The freezing is actually annoying anyway.
Okay, so it's kind of slow.
I would just have to massage this one until it works.
So what's the issue?
0.57 recharge.
Oh, yeah.
What is adding a lot?
This is removing recharge.
I made a huge mistake, guys.
Also, let me put these at this front here.
Protectile speed.
Light.
Time to experiment.
So it's recharged speed right now.
Okay.
Can I double dip on?
Oh, wait, almost.
Hold on.
It's actually a... So you see the damage?
Sometimes it's shooting when I'm low on mana.
It's like it's...
what is it?
What is it omitting is the question at low mana.
I remove this.
There's no double dip there.
One, two, three.
And then it should take a knot.
It should take that one on the second go around, no?
This one does reduce recharge time.
So if I just throw a bunch in the front.
So maybe this one is not actually worth it.
Just saying.
Oh, don't put it there.
Okay, and I'll throw this on.
Holy fucking shit.
Whoa, that's fast.
Ha!
That's somehow even faster than what I had before.
The fuck?
There it is.
Wow.
I'm buying this one so that I can replace the teleport if I find something great.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, now to make it even better.
Bloodlust?
Maybe.
No, that's too crazy.
What should I put on it?
Am I using everything?
Let's see here.
Four.
I could get rid of the light, I guess.
You don't really need it.
Let me just arrange it here.
It's a little unpredictable in that way.
I think I just want to throw on another triple.
Where did I put the triple?
There.
So one, two.
No, we don't actually have room for that.
But four of them is fine.
So one, two, three, four, we can add two more.
I don't want freeze.
That's perfect.
That is insane-o style.
Alright, that was a bit of a gamble there.
But it could have been cool.
I don't know.
You know, what if it put on something like always crit or something?
Actually, I don't even know if that's a spell, but something like that, you know?
Wait, I need to fix my first one, of course, and change these.
There we go.
Now this one right here is actually gonna make the healing faster.
Ah, fuck.
What about all these spells?
Just throw them on there, maybe?
Nah, that's too much mana.
I could turn this into my black hole wand and make it an insane wand.
Let's get rid of these things.
I don't actually want that.
Neither do I want this, or that.
I'll keep that.
Homing?
I don't know.
Null shot.
Increase the projectile's duration dramatically.
Maybe.
With the healing, maybe, it could be cool, right?
If I find a circle of healing.
You can even put a light on here, I guess.
There we go.
Freeze charge.
Maybe I get rid of the light shot.
Yeah, get out of here.
Okay, so that's a little bit chaotic, of course, because it's random.
That's the issue there.
Can I salvage that somehow, is the question.
Or do I need to... but then this is gonna be... Yeah, that ain't good.
That is bad.
The gods look the other way.
Good.
Wait, why doesn't this go in a ring?
Should it go in a ring still, though?
Removes all damage.
Why the hell is this...
creates a copy of the last spell.
Ah, that makes no sense, but sure.
I mean, better than nothing.
It's a heal.
It works in a pinch.
That's all that matters.
Let's go.
Let's see the wand in action.
It's definitely worse.
Definitely less damage on it.
But such is the price you pay when you gamble.
Almost hit that one, too, by the way.
What do we have here?
What's that?
Gold is forever.
Gold nuggets never disappear.
Revenge tentacle, angry ghost.
I don't like any of these.
I hate them all.
Kinda just want to leave them.
Come back and reroll later.
Is that crazy?
Jesus Christ, the recoil.
What is going on?
Holy shit, this is so bad.
It's the damage plus, I think.
Like, it's actually impossible to position myself properly in combat.
The recall is that bad.
I'm so glad I took peace with the gods.
What's that?
No more shuffle.
Oh, revenge.
Oh, toxic immunity.
That's a no brainer.
No brainer, dude.
I'm just taking a stroll through your place here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
This is just incredible.
I am in Perkschleraffenland.
Permanent shield.
I like it.
Do it.
Just do it.
More perks.
I wish it would stop putting the message to the gods or angry.
I get it.
I fucking get it.
Look at the recoil.
I'm instantly on the other side of the screen.
Cordyceps.
Teleportitis.
Living on the edge.
I like that.
I'll take that.
Sure.
Yellow, nah.
What's that?
Magic arrow with trigger.
No, no thanks.
I'm good, bro.
It's really odd that there's no fog of war here.
Sweet.
I'm just speed running through this right now.
Is that?
We did it.
We freaking did it.
Amazing.
Now we gotta go to one more and have a blast.
Oh yeah.
Man, this healing is bad, by the way.
It's really bad.
Need a better wand for that.
Feels terrible throwing this wand away though, you know.
But salute the wand, you know.
O7's in the chat for that one, because I'm gonna be throwing it away very soon.
And it served us well.
It shall be gone.
It did well, but it's time to retire that wand.
But do I want to change with any of these right now?
Let me just see.
Maybe I do.
Actually, that one doesn't look too bad.
Neither does that one.
Actually, that's even better.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not bad at all.
Wait.
Ah, that's so annoying.
Put this here.
Throw these away.
Okay,
it's a little slow.
Let's make it faster.
Oh, we're back.
Oh, that's so much better.
Holy shit.
Beautiful.
I love that emote, guys.
That's exactly what I meant.
Well, I actually thought of just the O7, but I didn't know there was an actual emote for that.
That's perfect.
A proper burial for the wand of swiftness.
Restart?
Wait, why?
What do you mean restart?
What's going on?
End the run now?
Oh, really?
Okay.
I'm gonna make a copy of the world as well.
Why reading chat, sus?
I'm reading chat today, guys.
Well, not reading it all the time, but I have it open on the side.
Okay, I'm gonna find my folder.
I'm gonna make a copy of it.
Just in case.
In fact, I'm gonna do that after every session from now on.
Wait, I can't find it.
Appdata local low.
There it is.
Copy that over to my folder.
Let's just call it something else.
All right, takes a while.
Even though it's only 250 megabytes, it takes a while because there's so many different files, it seems.
So we make a backup of the world now and then I go back in.
So, so how did you know that now is the time to restart?
Can you explain that to me?
Is it something special that I did?
The amount of worlds you cross.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
So am I fine now?
If I log back in, it's okay, right?
There's no, there's no crash.
Okay, thanks.
All right, thanks guys.
You're the best.
All right, I'm gonna go find more perks now.
It's perk time.
Well, it's been perk time the last two hours, but we're gonna perk even harder now.
Look at all that gold.
In fact, I'm running kind of low on gold.
Whoa.
Plasma beam thrower.
That seems scary.
Boink.
And that's it.
We reached the end here.
I need another black hole one too, actually.
This one's shooting too slow.
And we can edit once everywhere now.
Oh, that's so weird.
Watch me speedrun now.
This may be a little risky.
Just go, just go, just go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Dude, the recoil is so big that I almost can't hit anyone without flying to the other side of the map.
I've got to find a reduced recoil for sure.
What's happening with the gravity sometimes?
Like that guy has a gravity field.
At mana.
Yo.
Thanks.
Oh man, being able to hot swap that is just immaculate.
Wait, hold on.
Wait a minute, wait, wait, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Oh, there's homing on us.
I was wondering.
Like what the fuck?
I thought it was just the enemies in this place that has some sort of effect going on.
I have no idea how that homing ended up there.
That was fun though.
Oh, not this place.
This place is dangerous.
Wow, he deflected my black hole.
What a guy.
Is this it?
Easy, easy.
Oh, this is second nature now.
That was a little bit risky.
Not gonna lie.
I was risking it a little bit.
Wow, it's kind of far up, isn't it?
Holy crap.
Oh my goodness.
This is one large lake.
We made it.
Oh, it's still called east.
Okay, I must have missed that before.
I thought it just didn't have a name anymore.
I can't even recognize the game I'm playing, guys.
This is weird.
This is the weirdest Noite experience I've ever had.
It truly does feel like I'm just defying, I don't know, some kind of natural law that shouldn't be defied.
Oh, that's polymorphine.
Whoa, what the hell was that?
I guess it's west of here?
Yeah, I'm getting so good at this.
Even more stuff.
Reluctals that fly into a small sector behind you disappear.
Or stainless armor.
Oh, that in combination with invisibility could be sick.
No, wait, I'm thinking of another one.
I'm thinking of the one where you remove stains quicker.
Never mind.
But this one is also good.
I'll take that.
I don't really want anything here.
I'm good.
You know what, I'm gonna go to the fungal cavern.
Look at how many enemies are on my radar.
Actually absurd.
Okay, I think I'm good.
Just wait, where am I going?
Oh, oh, that's a funny looking one.
Look at that.
Doesn't that look like a compound bow or one of these modern bows that have like wheels on them and shit.
Very cool.
What's that?
Explosion of thunder.
Yo, that sounds cool.
I actually keep this one.
An electric explosion.
Oh, shit.
Uh, I mean, that is kind of expensive mana wise.
But we have an extra add mana here.
It's not gonna be enough, is it?
110 mana.
Try it.
See what happens.
Oh, so it's only the first shot, I guess.
And then after that, you see how it goes back to there.
And then what if I now replace that one?
Wait,
that is actually destroying stuff.
Interesting.
Yo, look at all the brickwork here.
Weird.
What's this?
Another set of perc lottery.
Fuck yeah.
I mean, we're going maximum perk.
Why wouldn't I take it?
I like this.
I like it.
Oh, Jesus.
That is awesome.
Look at that.
This one is nuts.
Oh, I run out of mana quick with this one, though.
I really need to find myself some.
Oh,
man.
I love it.
That is so much fun.
You know what?
Why not?
I'll take this.
Yeah.
And that one can go somewhere.
I don't need it.
Oh, the eye.
Hold on.
Hopefully this still works.
I'm actually kind of slippery right now.
I need to be careful here.
Will it work?
Oh, no.
Maybe I did destroy too much.
Oh, OK.
Wait, what?
Wait, this looks different.
Protectile area teleport.
Large spitter bolt.
Are these?
Oh, man.
1315.
Let's see the stats here.
500, 149.
I mean, OK, it's shuffled.
It kind of sucks.
No, thanks.
OK.
Oh, man.
Oh, that's so nice.
Look at the particle effects there.
That is sexy.
You know, it's going to be great.
Watch this.
Some people.
Oh, I can't get enough.
That is incredible.
That guy got a taste of his own medicine just now.
He has been bullying people for the longest time.
No more.
I'm afraid of freezing vapor.
That's still a thing that can damage me.
I can't even tell what's happening on the screen.
This is just wild.
So I got to go turn in my broken wand.
That is too much fun.
Is it even here?
Oh, my God.
Oh, it kills things on the other side of the wall.
Wow.
That is too good.
Good thing I'm explosion immune, huh?
Oh, shit.
I don't see an animal.
Maybe it's not here.
What?
OK.
It's a bummer.
Huh.
All right.
I kind of want to go visit the spiders.
I just need to see if I can finally kill them with what I've got going on here.
It's got to be right.
It's got to be time.
Hi, man.
What's this?
You currently held wand loses half its capacity.
No, no, no, no, no.
You can fly 100% longer.
Oh, that's actually not too bad.
Oh, we can take more.
But I don't like any of the rest.
Unless I want to use it on some other one.
You couldn't hit one.
There's gains more mana.
How if it's maybe that one.
Or that one.
No, that's half of this is going to be.
I don't know.
What would that be if it's five?
Will it round down or round up?
I don't know, man.
Another damage.
Another quick recharge.
I mean, I don't think I ever want bloodlust.
It's too dangerous.
And I have this one.
If I need to damage myself with a deadly heal, should be okay.
Throw that away.
Take it back.
Hey there, dude.
I think I'll take this one too.
So wait, if I...
I wonder if this is worth it because you shoot everything off at once and you go into all of them at once, you get the full heal, right?
I'm going to experiment with that.
This one, though, I don't want.
How's everybody doing down here, huh?
I'm going to go say hi to the spiders.
I need to see if I can kill them now.
They have some sort of weird self-healing going on that I haven't quite gotten to the bottom of yet.
Oh.
Necromancy.
Dude, having the vision everywhere is actually nuts.
Oh!
Oh wait, I'm immune to them.
Wow, he just can't die.
Well, I can't die either.
It's like when an immovable object hits an unstoppable force.
Well, I'm going to explore your fucking home now, if you don't mind.
Now that you can't hurt me, I feel comfortable going around here.
Seeing the little clouds off screen is actually massive.
Changes everything.
I don't even know what's happening.
I liked it.
This game has become something different now.
And I don't mind.
It's cool.
That just bounced off a shield.
Wait, they have the thingy going on.
Wait, let me see here.
So if I do this...
Oh, it's totally not worth it with the quick recharge.
I think what's happening is it's spending so much mana that it doesn't get to shoot enough projectiles off.
So the healing is actually less in the long run.
What's that?
I don't know.
I think I reckon it's like a some kind of bounce, bubbly bounce or something.
Something like it.
It's getting a little sketchy here.
Oh, clouds!
Reduce lifetime.
There's actually a lot of wands in here.
It's kind of a cool place.
For finding wands.
Not bad.
I feel like this is a great opportunity to just explore parts of the world that I don't normally explore, because I have full vision.
I get to see things.
Like what the hell?
Wait a minute.
Has that always?
Hold up a second here.
I'm in the luki lair.
There's a freaking thingy in there.
No way.
Stealing that.
I'm not sure exactly where in here.
I'm just gonna put it somewhere for now.
Is there a tablet?
There is.
All right.
Take it!
I may actually have made a mistake.
Do we have enough healing?
Actually, hold
on.
I can remove this.
I keep forgetting I have a tinker.
Oh, shit.
You know what?
Put this here for now.
Oh, shit.
That adds.
That's bad.
Okay, stop.
It's stopped.
We're fine.
We're back.
Wouldn't it be funny if this actually killed him?
Does that kill you?
Get away from me.
I wonder what does kill these guys.
Two and a half K HP.
Holy shit.
That's the most I've ever had.
This run has become something else.
What am I even looking for?
Look for once.
Okay, I think I'm good.
Let's keep going.
I don't even know what the fuck I am.
Okay, I'm here.
Oh, man.
Here we go.
Weakening curse explosives.
Now, now, now.
Isn't that interesting?
50 mana drain, though.
It's getting a little too much.
Maybe.
Yeah, it's not sustainable.
Not yet, at least.
Not yet.
What's this?
Rage, fuel, levitation, exploding gold.
Man, I don't like any of these goddamn perks.
Killing an enemy makes you replenish some of your... I mean, I'll take that.
At least that's not a curse in any way.
Kill them all.
Oh my god, my game is lagging.
Hopefully not a sign that something is about to crash.
What the
hell?
Oh, stronger hearts again?
Something's a happy minion who'll eat enemy projectile every now and then.
Oh, right.
Sure.
Okay, I'll take it.
Fine.
Taking all the perks.
Further down.
True orbit.
Oh wait, that's it.
God, dude, look at all the perks we have.
Holy shit.
Is it time?
You know what?
I'm gonna go through here now.
Yep.
I think I'm gonna go left.
Hold on, actually while I'm here.
I am in the art.
I could try to go here again.
Or I could also just go left this time.
Yeah.
Oh, but wait, if I have to go left, I have to go quite far.
I would have to go all the way through here.
Across the ocean.
Hold on, what else do I have on my list of to-do things?
What am I actually trying to do here?
I've gotten so carried away with the perks, I kind of forgot my purpose.
Try cave music with music.
Oh, right.
Okay.
So now I know where I want to go.
Explore the heavens above pond slash lake.
Because up there, we also have more musical notes.
And we can find an F most likely.
That's the goal right now.
That's what we're gonna do.
And of course, we also have the goal of finding some actual healing spell that doesn't suck.
We're gonna go to the heaven.
And oh, switch back.
I heard the music.
The system works.
What is this one again?
Swapper.
It was theorized that the source of qualia would be transferred.
But it turns out it was the whole body all along.
What the fuck does qualia mean?
I'm not sure.
I feel like that that's a big lore piece here about the world.
Quality.
Don't go that way.
That's a bad idea.
I may just... Actually, hold on.
I have a better way to go to the surface.
Watch this.
Uh...
Yo,
I wonder if there's an equivalent place like this...
in the other worlds.
Yeah, there we go.
There we go.
This may not actually be faster in hindsight.
Whoa.
Okay.
I think I'll just go along one edge here.
Sup fools.
Oh, that was a polymorph man.
Oh, I'm so glad that wasn't polymorphism.
Dude, I kind of want to see what's on the other side there.
Uh, return...
Heal.
I do wonder where I actually am in the world.
Hold on, let me go to the top.
The plan is to go to an important area, such as the top where their portal is.
And then we're gonna try and go left, right, up and down.
Well, not down, because we came from down.
You know what I mean.
We have arrived in hell.
That's it.
We made it.
There it is.
Okay, so I was here last.
Let's try going up.
Oh, we gotta heal first.
Also, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Over here.
What could I try here?
Hold on.
Friendship or avarice?
Actually, this one is kind of useless for me right now.
Oh, actually, wait a minute.
Oh, okay.
There's also cursed rock here.
You know what?
Let's go left first.
Oh, hold on.
I need to heal.
I don't know how far this is gonna go.
Okay, that was actually fast healing.
All right, go!
Oh, that wasn't too bad!
Wait, what?
Where am I?
Where the fuck am I?
He got blown up.
I mean, this looks like a place I've been before.
Well, I don't want to get too lost.
Came from here.
Let's just stay on the left path.
Left from here.
Oh, wait!
The moon!
So, I'm to the right?
Wait, what?
The fuck is that?
No way!
That's where... Excuse me.
That's where I teleported to earlier.
Wait, wait a minute.
Where is this?
So, I'm like 15 degrees from the moon.
So, this way.
Something like that, I would approximate, given my... given where the moon is located.
So, we don't need... we don't know the distance here.
D.
Well, uh, let's think.
We were at...
We are in the frozen.
Snowy depths.
So, I guess we are here.
But this is just a rough estimate, by the way.
It's like 10 to 25 degrees, I would say.
From the center.
So, really, we should be...
somewhere here.
That's what I'm gonna say.
Somewhere here.
Let's keep exploring.
Let's just see if we can find some landmarks.
Okay, so...
From here...
This is a landmark, right?
This is a landmark.
Let's try going straight down.
Let's see what we end up.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck is this?
What the hell is that?
Wait, what?
Oh!
Oh, wait, I've been here!
I've been...
Ah, okay.
Awesome.
Let's try going north.
Uh, wrong side, I think.
Don't jump in the portal.
Holy shit!
Dude, I estimated perfectly!
I estimated perfectly!
I'm here!
That's amazing.
So, wait, uh...
So, we have a...
room...
with a portal.
Wait a minute.
Show me the shape of the room that I enjoy.
Okay, it's like a weird... I sort of destroyed the room, I guess.
So, there's like a room here.
Looks like a potato, okay?
That's the room.
We have a portal.
Actually, make the potato a little thinner.
Like that.
And then we're gonna steal some artwork I made earlier.
From here.
Thank you!
Bring that over here.
Boink!
There we go.
And then inside of here...
We're gonna have a little bit of a...
there's a path.
I guess you could say.
Walk along that.
It looks like...
like a dragon from Rainworld.
This is the eye.
That's the mouth.
That's kind of funny.
Okay, and below that...
Oh, we got a test!
Oh, we got a test with the platform room after this.
So, then we have this weird room.
Also a potato, a different potato.
And there's these weird pillars.
We have a lot of sand.
In between.
This is to be predified later, don't worry.
It's ugly now.
And then we have some sort of platform in the center.
Where there was a big bowl.
If you remember that.
It's right below that.
The rest here is also sand, I guess.
Until you uncover it.
Amazing.
Okay, so now I want to check.
If I go straight down from there, will I encounter the platform room?
Let's see!
Straight down.
Well, almost straight down, I guess.
I can't trust my drawing.
I'm assuming straight down.
Okay, actually nothing yet.
So wait, is my drawing that fucking accurate?
So if I go a little left...
Wait a minute, there's no way.
There's no way I'm that good.
Maybe not.
I probably got the location of that wrong.
Let me try something else.
From this room...
Let's go left.
That way.
This has proven to be such a good strategy for exploring.
Find a landmark and go cardinal directions.
Aha!
Wait a minute, where did that lead again?
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
I'm getting to the bottom of this.
Oh!
Easy base?
What about down?
Oh, looky, looky layer.
Oh my god!
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
I actually don't know what this is.
Why did I put this here?
What even is this?
I... I must have put that there for a reason.
Let's leave it.
Oh, that works out beautifully too.
It's right there.
No.
No!
Make it smaller, please.
There we go.
That actually looks really cool.
We're gonna call it...
You're not gonna guess.
It's gonna be the...
Oculus...
Rift.
No, just Oculus.
No, ocular.
Ocular room.
I like that name.
The ocular room.
Very nice.
Save it.
So when we go straight down, we reach looky layer.
Oh man, it's perfect!
It's so good.
Also, I hit these lines that I made here.
Ugliness, get rid of it.
Yep.
So the platform room is not located there, I guess.
I guess I put that one.
So I know it's to the right of the Dragon Cave.
So that means...
It's somewhere along this line of...
side here, I guess.
So it is somewhere along here.
I just need to find it, I guess.
Pretty sick.
Dude, this is so much fun.
I love it.
Back up.
Whoa.
Oh, that was weird.
Straight up.
Let me just confirm exactly where I end up.
Oh!
Magical temple!
No fucking shit!
Well, I guess it's not that weird.
Makes sense.
This is the way I... Oh, it's beautiful!
Look!
My map is accurate.
This is actually so reassuring, you know?
It's such nice reaffirming feeling.
That's amazing.
Probably the size of this is smaller in reality, but you know, it's there now.
It's beautiful.
We should give this a name.
This room will be called...
How do we get in there again?
Was that via the hourglass?
No, no, the hourglass took us to the eye.
This one we got to via...
What?
I forgot where this one...
Where we came from there.
This room down here I can call...
No, hold on.
Hell's Kitchen.
That's a part of New York, right?
It just looks like a kitchen to me.
What can I say?
This one up here shall be named...
Um...
Just... I guess just the haberdashery.
I'm getting haberdashery vibes.
I like it.
Okay.
Oh, wait, wait!
No, never mind.
So that leads to the tower.
And when I went...
Oh, but hold on a second.
Wait a second now.
This all started...
from the tower.
I went... Wait, how does this make any sense?
Nothing doesn't add up.
I think I'm misremembering what I just did like 10 minutes ago.
So I was in the tower.
I dug from here.
I arrived there.
I did not take the portal.
Instead, I went this way.
And I dug and I dug and I dug.
And what did I find?
I must have... Oh!
No, wait, wait.
What did I find?
Okay, guys, I'm actually gonna ask you.
I can't take this right here.
I'm actually... I'm hating myself.
What did I find right... just before when I went left of the tower?
Can you tell me?
The haberdashery?
Wait, wait, wait.
What?
You first found a big empty vertical space.
Oh, you're right.
You're right.
That's true.
Yeah, yeah.
Diamond, crystal, friend, or Everest.
Yeah, I remember that.
But then I went more west from there, didn't I?
Oh, I guess... Yeah, I was about to say the haberdashery is not there.
It's here.
So the only explanation then...
is that...
Hold on, I can actually just confirm this myself.
Hold on.
This is... there's a way better way of doing this.
Wait a second here.
Whoops.
Oh!
Oh, no.
I destroyed it!
No, it's still here.
Oh, nice.
Portal doesn't disappear.
So I came from here...
Wait.
Hell's Kitchen?
Uh, wait, wait, this doesn't make any fucking sense.
Habberdashery.
No, wait.
Hell's Kitchen?
I'm Hell's Kitchen now.
And if I go left from there...
What the fuck?
Easy pace.
Does that make sense?
Actually, it does make sense.
Never mind.
It makes total sense.
Yeah, it makes total sense.
Perfect.
So I'm gonna draw here this little outcropping.
Like that.
I actually forgot to do this earlier.
And then above that...
We have this little area.
Shaped like that.
Okay.
Zoom in.
Make it a little bit smaller.
Something like that, you know.
Oh.
And inside of there.
We have a nice...
Good enough for now.
Requires...
Uh, what was it?
Unstable?
Or I guess just teleportation of some sort.
Teleportation.
And then down here we had the shop.
And the shop looks like...
That.
Gotcha.
Let me make a straight line.
Gotta make it look nice, you know.
And it's located on top of a little...
I don't even know, like... piece of rock.
Something like that.
I'm gonna call it...
Uh, let's call it...
Whole Foods.
It's like the smaller version of the wand mart.
Even though it's not wands, it's spells.
Easy peasy.
The map is getting detailed here, huh?
It's really coming together!
God damn!
Love it!
Speaking of spells.
True orbit.
Summon platform.
Not intrigued.
So hold on.
Go back here now?
This was not the thing I actually wanted to confirm.
So if I go up here now...
I am here.
And I came from the right...
Big open area.
That's right.
And that was back to the tower.
Let me just confirm that.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah!
Yes, dude!
Okay!
Oh, hold on a second then.
By the way, I think these are way smaller.
Let's just make them a bit smaller.
Like that.
I'm gonna remove...
some of this.
No fucking way.
That shit was... I guess I put this here just because I didn't know where it was.
Which makes sense, but now we know where it is.
I'll leave that there for now.
Whoops.
I'm gonna say there.
Something like that.
And the meat realm is right above?
Hold on, we gotta check that.
We gotta check that out.
Okay, let's see now.
Let's see if I'm correct here.
Let's try going straight... hold on, let me heal.
Go up first.
Lovely.
What?
Wait, where the fuck am I?
Oh!
Ah, cursed rock!
The cursed...
That actually makes total sense!
I saw that was cursed rock there.
That's the tower!
Oh man!
That felt good.
Okay.
That's great.
Hold on, whoops, turn it over a little more.
Like that.
There it is.
Beautiful.
So obviously what we gotta do now is to make a beautiful line here from the tower.
Boink!
Nah, I'm kidding.
That's ugly as fuck.
We don't need that.
Ah!
No idea how I made that line.
It was kind of exciting though.
Okay, put this here.
Make it a little thicker.
Boink!
Yeah.
Okay.
Things are coming together here.
Dude, if you look at this map here...
This is really insane!
So you start off the game...
knowing about this, right?
Or even more specifically, you're like...
This is what you know when you start the game.
That's your whole world.
That's your world view.
But it's much more than that.
It's crazy.
Crazy.
Okay, very nice.
Meat realm.
So the meat realm, exactly where is that located then?
Because I'm not going through it on my way.
That means it's above, right?
That means... I think it's in the right spot here.
That makes sense.
Yeah.
This place we need to explore more for sure.
The wizard's den is a conundrum.
There's a boss down here.
I should note that actually.
Hey!
You!
Yeah, you.
There's a...
boss here.
Neat, huh?
That's for later.
Now I will never forget.
Okay.
There's a boss there, and there's also... Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I think I have proportions wrong here.
There's something I never added, by the way.
We know there's one of these rooms here somewhere.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Proportions are all wrong.
This can't be right.
Is it really that thin?
More like that?
We know there's one of these there.
Yep.
That makes sense.
And then the cave sort of uh...
does one of these.
We can finally connect the line.
That line has been sitting there since the start of the goddamn game.
I like it.
I like it a lot.
Guys.
That's got to be it for me.
This time around.
I will make a backup of this world immediately.
Actually,
I'm going to put it back on the map.
So we have some music.
I should probably put it in such that the music also plays during the wadescreen.
How we doing?
We need a cacao emoji?
You're right, we do.
How would that look?
Where was your stretch break?
Ah, fuck.
Goddammit.
There's something about Neutze where you just get completely absorbed.
And time loses all meaning and you just fly.
I don't I don't know how to explain it.
I completely forgot to take a break.
Goddammit.
It would take a car on it.
Oh, okay.
A bird?
It seems as though you like this game.
I like this game.
Yeah, can you can you tell?
I've only played like how many hours is it now?
Let me see.
169 hours.
169.9 hours on Steam.
That's a lot.
That those numbers mean that I played a lot.
Yeah, I like the game.
That's a clear indicator.
You did great today.
Thank you, Psycaten.
Thank you very much.
Oh, Sekhmet.
Thanks for subscribing.
I don't know if you're here.
Sekhmet underscore and Stuks Eftika.
Subscribe for six months.
Thank you so much Stuks.
Or Stiks.
Let me know how to pronounce it.
That's really nice of you.
And Dragonfire also.
973.
Not to be confused with the other 972 Dragonfires.
Dragonfire 973 is the real one.
Oliver, I think you should find and watch the worst guide to Noite.
There are no longer any major spoilers for you there and your reaction is going to be interesting.
Oh, yeah?
Do people agree in that?
Huguenomikron.
Maybe you need a few hours more just to be sure.
Yeah, you know, if it's below 180, you can't really be sure whether or not you like a game.
But above that, completely.
Also, Oliver, I mentioned a bit back Dremal, an adventure map for Minecraft, recently started it myself and goodness, is it so much more than I explained it.
Oh, yeah?
Well, here's the thing.
Minecraft is a never ending game.
Infinite content the way I see it.
We're gonna have time for that.
There's so many more things to do also right now.
But I'm not opposed to it, Hive.
I'm not opposed to it.
It sounds fun.
Can you add the cursed rock around the tower back in your map?
Yeah, of course.
I can do that.
I can do that while we talk.
Oh, we can even make it look nice.
It's sort of reddish, actually, that rock, right?
We're gonna do this.
How about that?
Actually, even better.
Wait a minute.
Danger zone.
This is temporary.
We can make this look better later.
Look at that.
Wait, is it greenish?
Am I color blind?
Wait, really?
No, it's red.
It's reddish.
No.
Okay.
Should be red.
Okay, okay.
I thought I was losing my mind there for a minute.
Also,
the orb room was right above the tower in your map.
It is too much way up.
I mean, yeah, I'm sure it's not accurate.
All that stuff is gonna get fixed in time.
I've had things in the wrong places for the longest time.
And then when you finally realize where it is, it's such a good feeling.
I'll fix that too.
I'll fix that too at some point.
This song is making me want to live in Hellenest.
I know.
It's so damn good.
It's my favorite track, I think.
Wait, this is from Dirtmouth, right?
Actually, I think my favorite track is from the Hallowed Grounds, I think it's called.
How much more do you think you'll play Noita?
I think it's one of those games I'll play once in a blue moon.
But I'm gonna cut down on it drastically soon.
So maybe when this run ends, I'm gonna be playing it way less.
Just because there are so many other games I want to play, I also started Minecraft.
And I'll be starting Dredge as well.
I mean, yeah, I'll still be playing it, but just not at the same rate, I guess.
I've been playing it for 170 hours now already, you know?
Think about it like this.
If I were to die in a car accident tomorrow, I would have missed out on so many other games.
I want to get to experience them all.
Dredge on stream?
No, that's gonna be local recording.
Are you excited for Dredge?
It won by a clear margin.
People are excited about it, it seems.
Okay, guys, it's time for me to head on out.
I'm actually getting... I have a bit of a pain in my stomach for some reason.
I don't know.
It's not that I'm hungry.
It's a bit weird.
Maybe I just need to eat something.
Anyway, thank you so much for watching.
Let's rate someone on the way out.
Someone who's streaming Neutze.
Or not.
Hold on.
How about... same category.
Okiniva.
I'm sending you over to Okiniva.
He's going for a win in Neutze.
Okay, guys, thanks for watching, subscribing, and just hanging out.
It's awesome.
I'll see you on the Discord if you haven't been there yet.
Please go there.
It's an awesome place.